suman in this workshop draws
from his vast experience and shares
frameworks on how to understand and
interpret the change that is happening
he gives us methodologies and frameworks
on
how to react and respond because the
organization for the future
will not survive by making a 10
improvement
it needs a 10x transformation and the
massive transformation
case studies that someone gives in this
workshop
have helped me plan my business
as an entrepreneur and has made me that
much better
thank you and i would strongly recommend
the exponential innovation series to
any businessman leader or an
entrepreneur